<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<NameGen>
  <Join>
    <Join sep=" ">
      <Switch id="gender">
        <Join sep=" ">
          <Option id="title" probability="0.3">
            <Words>
              Adm. Baron Capt. Cmdr. Cmdre. Col. Count DCI Dr. Earl Gen. Granddad HRH HRM
              Insp. Lord Lt. Mr. PC Prince Prof. Sen. Sgt. Sir Sr. Uncle
            </Words>
          </Option>
          <Repeat min="1" max="2">
            <Join>
              <Option probability="0.1">
                <Words>
                  Mc
                </Words>
              </Option>
              <Markov id="firstname" target_len="5" cutoff_len="12">
                Abraham Achilles Adam Adolphus Alastair Albert Aldous Alexander Alfred Algernon
                Aloysius Alphonse Alvin Angus Antonio Anubis Apollo Apophis Archibald Archilles
                Ares Arnold Arthur Atlas Augustus Aurelius Avery Axel Azrael Barbarossa
                Bartholomew Baxter Beelzebub Benjamin Beowulf Bernard Beverly Bill Billy Blake
                Bob Bobby Bogart Boris Bradbury Braxton Broderick Brody Buckminster Burnaby
                Buster Calvin Carlson Ceasar Charlemagne Charlie Chester Christopher Clarence
                Clifford Clinton Clyde Colby Colin Columbus Conrad Cornelius Cosmo Cronus
                Dashiell Davy Delbert Desmond Dexter Dimitri Dionysus Dominic Donald Donovan
                Dorian Douglas Dracula Drake Dudley Duncan Dwayne Dwight Edgar Edison Edmund
                Edward Edwin Egbert Einstein Elmer Elon Emerson Emory Enzo Ephraim Erasmus
                Excalibur Ezekiel Ezra Fabian Fairbanks Felix Ferdinand Fergus Finn Finnegan
                Fitzgerald Fitzpatrick Fletcher Frankenstein Frankie Franklin Freddy Frederick
                Fritz Furio Gabriel Genghis Geoffrey Gerald Gideon Gilbert Giles Godfrey Gordon
                Graham Grant Gregory Grover Guillermo Gus Gustav Hades Hannibal Harold Harrison
                Harry Harvey Heathcliff Hector Helios Henry Hephaestus Herbert Herman Hermes
                Homer Horace Horatio Horus Howard Howell Hubert Hudson Hugo Humphrey Huxley Hyde
                Hyperion Hypnos Ian Icarus Ictor Ignatius Immanuel Irving Isaac Isaiah Isidore
                Ismael Ivan James Janus Jefferson Jehovah Jekyll Jenkins Jeremiah Jethro Jimbo
                Jimbob Jimmy Johnny Jonathan Joseph Joshua Judas Julius Jupiter Kennedy Kerberos
                Lancelot Laszlo Lawrence Leonard Leonidas Leopold Leroy Lincoln Lionel Loki
                Lorenzo Louis Lucas Lucifer Lucius Luther Lysander Marcellus Marcus Mars Martin
                Maximus Maxwell Melvin Mephisto Mephistopheles Mercury Merlin Merrick Metatron
                Michael Midas Miles Milton Moby Modred Mohammed Montgomery Mordecai Mordred
                Moriarty Morpheus Mortimer Moses Muhammad Murphy Murray Mustafa Napoleon Nathan
                Nathaniel Neptune Neville Newton Nigel Norbert Norman Norris Norton O' O'Brian
                O'Connor O'Donnell O'Farrell O'Finnegan O'Flaherty O'Flynn O'Gara O'Grady O'Hare
                O'Leary O'Malley O'Mara O'Neill O'Rourke O'Sullivan O'Toole Oberon Octavius Odin
                Odysseus Oliver Orion Orlando Orson Orville Oscar Osiris Oswald Otto Owen Ozzy
                Paisley Pan Patrick Percival Percy Perry Perseus Peter Philip Phineas Phoenix
                Pluto Pollywog Ponce Pontius Porter Poseidon Prescott Preston Prometheus Ptolemy
                Quasimodo Quentin Quigley Quincy Quixote Ra Randall Randolph Reginald Renfield
                Roderick Roland Roosevelt Rudolph Rufus Rumpelstiltskin Rupert Rurik Satan
                Saturn Seamus Sebastian Seymour Sheldon Sherlock Sigmund Sinclair Sisyphus
                Solomon Stanley Stanton Sterling Stetson Sullivan Sylvester Thackeray Thaddeus
                Thanatos Theodore Theseus Thomas Thor Throckmorton Thurston Timothy Titus Tobias
                Toby Todd Tom Tommy Torquil Torrance Trenton Tristan Troy Truman Tucker Turner
                Tycho Tyler Tyson Ulrich Ulysses Umberto Upton Uriel Victor Vincent Virgil
                Vladimir Voltaire Vulcan Waldo Wallace Walter Washington Watson Wayne Webster
                Wenslydale Wesley Wheeler Whittaker Wilburforce Wilfred William Willoughby
                Wilson Winston Wolfgang Woodrow Wyatt Xander Xavier Xeno Xerxes Xylon Zacharias
                Zachary Zane Zebedee Zephyr Zeus
              </Markov>
            </Join>
          </Repeat>
          <Option probability="0.1">
            <Words>
              von
            </Words>
          </Option>
        </Join>
        <Join sep=" ">
          <Option id="title" probability="0.2">
            <Words>
              Adm. Aunt Baroness Capt. Cmdr. Cmdre. Col. Countess DCI Dame Dr. Gen. Grandma
              HRH HRM Insp. Lt. Mdme. Mrs. Ms. PC Princess Prof. Sen. Sgt. Sra. Srta.
            </Words>
          </Option>
          <Repeat min="1" max="2">
            <Markov id="firstname" target_len="5" cutoff_len="12">
              Agatha Agnes Amelia Angelica Annabelle Antonia Aphrodite Arabella Aria Ariadne
              Ariel Artemis Astrid Atalanta Athena Audrey Augusta Barbara Bast Beatrice
              Bernadette Bernadine Bernice Beryl Beverly Bianca Bonita Bonnie Bridget Bronwyn
              Brooke Bryony Buffy Buttercup Calypso Caroline Cassandra Catherine Catrina
              Cecilia Celeste Celia Charity Charlene Charlotte Chastity Chelsea Cheryl Chloe
              Christabel Christina Christine Cinderella Cindy Claire Clarissa Claudia
              Clementine Cleopatra Cordelia Cornelia Courtney Crystal Cynthia Daisy Danielle
              Daphne Debbie Deborah Deirdre Delilah Demeter Desdemona Diana Dolores Dominique
              Donna Dorothea Drusilla Eastasia Edith Edna Eileen Elaine Eleanor Elena
              Elizabeth Emilia Emily Emma Enid Enya Erica Esme Esmeralda Estelle Esther Ethel
              Eudora Eugenia Euphemia Eurydice Evangeline Evelyn Faith Fallon Felicia Felicity
              Fiona Flora Florence Francesca Franny Freya Frida Gabriella Galadriel Galatea
              Gale Genevieve Gertrude Ginny Giselle Gloria Grace Griselda Guenevere Guinevere
              Gwendolyn Harriet Hazel Hecate Helena Henrietta Hera Hesperia Hestia Hilda
              Hildegarde Holly Hortense Hyacinth Hypatia Imogen Ingrid Irene Iris Isabella
              Isadora Isis Isolde Ivana Ivy Janice Jardine Jasmine Jeanette Jemima Jessica
              Joan Jocelyn Josephine Joyce Judith Julia Juliana Juliette Juno Laura Lavinia
              Leona Leonora Letitia Lilith Lillian Lilliput Lizzie Lucinda Lucretia Lucy
              Ludmilla Luna Lyra Lysistrata Madeline Magdalen Magnolia Matilda Maureen Maxine
              Mercedes Mercy Meredith Millicent Minerva Miranda Morgana Myrtle Nancy Naomi
              Natalie Natasha Nell Nemesis Nicole Nicolette Nike Nina Noel Nora Norah Nyx
              Pamela Pandora Pansy Parvati Pascale Patricia Penelope Persephone Philippa
              Phoebe Phyllis Polly Portia Priscilla Prudence Pulchritude Rachel Ramona Rebecca
              Regina Renata Rhea Rhiannon Rhoda Rosalind Rosalyn Rosamund Rosemary Rowena
              Roxanne Sabrina Samantha Sarah Selene Serena Shasta Sheridan Sibyl Siren Sophia
              Stella Stephanie Styx Susan Susannah Sylvia Tabitha Tammy Thalia Thelma Themis
              Theodora Theresa Tilly Titania Trixie Ursula Valentina Vanessa Venus Verona
              Veronica Vesper Victoria Violet Violetta Virginia Vivian Vivienne Wanda Wendy
              Wilhelmina Willa Winifred Winona Wren Xena Yvonne Zelda Zora
            </Markov>
          </Repeat>
          <Option probability="0.1">
            <Words>
              van
            </Words>
          </Option>
        </Join>
      </Switch>
      <Join>
        <Option probability="0.1">
          <Words>
            Mc
          </Words>
        </Option>
        <Markov id="surname" target_len="6" cutoff_len="12">
          Aardvark Abacus Abbey Aberration Abracadabra Absurdity Accident Accolade
          Addendum Adjective Aerodrome Albatross Albertosaurus Alligator Allosaurus
          Aluminum Amargasaurus Amoeba Anaconda Anemone Ankylosaurus Anomaly Antelope
          Antenna Antlion Anvil Apatosaurus Ape Apocalypse Apparatus Aquarium Aqueduct
          Arboretum Argentinosaurus Armadillo Armageddon Armchair Armory Armpit Arpeggio
          Arquebus Artichoke Artifact Artificer Ascot Asparagus Asteroid Astronaut Asylum
          Atom Auditorium Automaton Automobile Aviator Avocado Baboon Backgammon Bacon
          Badger Bagel Balaclava Ballistic Bamboo Banana Bandana Banjo Barbecue Barometer
          Barracuda Barricade Baryon Baryonyx Basilisk Bastion Bathtub Bazinga Beachball
          Beagle Beanstalk Bear Beaver Bed Beehive Beetle Beret Berry Bicycle Bigears
          Bigfoot Bighead Bigmouth Bignose Bigwig Billygoat Biscotti Blackhole Blimp Bling
          Blorp Blubber Blunderbuss Bobsled Bonobo Boondoggle Bork Borscht Boson Bowtie
          Brachiosaurus Brain Broccoli Brogues Brontosaurus Broomstick Brownie Bubblewrap
          Buffalo Bugle Bulldozer Bullfrog Bumblebee Bungalow Bunsen Buoy Bureau Burner
          Burrito Cabbage Cactus Candelabra Candy Cannoli Cannon Cantaloupe Cappuccino
          Caramel Carbon Caribou Carnival Carnotaurus Carrot Cartographer Cartoon
          Cartwheel Cashew Cassowary Catastrophe Caterpillar Catfish Caviar Cellophane
          Cellphone Centaur Chair Chameleon Chandelier Chariot Charlatan Cheese
          Cheeseburger Chicken Chimpanzee Chinchilla Chipmunk Chupacabra Circus Clockwork
          Clown Clownfish Cockatoo Coconut Coffee Coffeepot Comet Compendium Confetti
          Contraption Corgi Cornflake Cornucopia Crab Crocodile Croissant Cucumber
          Cuddlebug Cummerbund Cupboard Cupcake Curmudgeon Cutlery Cuttlefish Cyborg
          Dachshund Dandelion Deuterium Dimension Dimetrodon Dingo Dinosaur Diplodocus
          Discotheque Dodecahedron Doodad Doodle Doodlebug Doohickey Doughnut Dragonfly
          Dromedary Dynamite Earthling Eggplant Electron Elephant Elevator Emu Enchilada
          Encyclopedia Espresso Excavator Eyeball Eyepatch Facepalm Faceplant Falafel
          Fedora Fermion Ferret Fettuccine Fireplace Fish Fishstick Flamingo
          Flibbertigibbet Flowerpot Fluffypants Foobar Foundation Frankenstein Fridge
          Gadgetry Galaxy Garden Gazelle Gelato Gerbil Giganotosaurus Gimbal Giraffe Gizmo
          Gluon Gnocchi Gobbledygook Goblin Goldfish Golem Gorilla Graviton Gremlin
          Grendel Gymnasium Habanero Hadron Haggis Hamburger Hedgehog Helicopter Helium
          Hippogriff Hippopotamus Hobgoblin Hotdog Houseplant Hummus Hydogen Hydrant
          Hyperboloid Hypercube Hypersphere Ibex Ibis Igloo Ignoramus Iguana Impala
          Infographic Infomercial Insect Insomniac Jackalope Jalapeno Jellyfish Jetpack
          Kaiju Kangaroo Knitwear Koala Kraken Krampus Kumquat Labradoodle Labyrinth
          Lasagna Latte Lemming Lemur Lepton Linguine Littlebottom Littlefoot Littlenose
          Llama Lobster Locomotive Lollipop Lollygag Longears Longnose Longtoes
          Loudspeaker Luffa Lugnut Lumberjack Lunatic Lycanthrope Macaron Macaroni Macaw
          Macchiato Magician Malarkey Mallard Mammoth Manatee Manifold Mapusaurus
          Marshmallow Martian Marzelvane Mastodon Mathematician Meatball Megaphone Melon
          Menagerie Merlot Metaverse Meteor Meteoroid Mongoose Monocle Moon Moonbeam
          Moorhen Moped Motorcycle Muffin Muffler Multiverse Mushroom Nautilus Nebula
          Necktie Nectarine Nematode Neptunium Neutron Ninja Nitrogen Noodle Nunchuck
          Octopus Ogre Orangutan Ostrich Owlbear Oxygen Oyster Pancake Pangolin Panini
          Panorama Parabola Paradox Parasol Parrot Peacock Pelican Pentaceratops
          Philosopher Phosphorus Photon Pillbug Pillow Pirate Pixie Planet Planetarium
          Platypus Plesiosaur Plutocracy Plutocrat Plutonium Pogo Polyglot Polyhedron
          Polymath Polymorph Pomegranate Pomeranian Poodle Popcorn Popsicle Porcupine
          Porkpie Porpoise Potato Potterverse Poutine Pretzel Propellor Protoceratops
          Proton Proudbottom Proudears Proudfoot Proudnose Psudonym Psudopod Psychopomp
          Pterodactyl Pufferfish Pumpkin Pyjamas Python Quark Quasar Qubit Quesadilla
          Quetzalcoatl Quetzalcoatlus Quiche Quinoa Rabbit Raccoon Racecar Racehorse
          Radish Ramen Raptor Raspberry Rattlesnake Ravioli Raygun Reality Reindeer
          Rhinoceros Rhubarb Robot Rockfish Roflcopter Rutabaga Salamander Samosa Sandwich
          Sasquatch Satellite Sculpture Seagull Seahorse Selenium Shawarma Shellfish
          Shrimp Silicon Simulation Singularity Skateboard Skeleton Slop Snickerdoodle
          Snorkel Snugglesworth Spacecraft Spaghetti Spam Spatula Sphinx Spinosaurus
          Sponge Spork Sprinkles Sprocket Spud Spumoni Spurtle Squabble Squash Squeegee
          Squelch Squid Squirrel Star Starfish Stegosaurus Strawberry Sturgeon Submarine
          Succotash Sulfur Sushi Suspenders Swordfish Synergy Synthesizer Tandoori Tapir
          Teapot Teddybear Tempura Tentacle Tesseract Theologian Thingamabob Thingamajig
          Tiramisu Toadstool Toaster Tofu Tomato Toothbrush Toothpaste Toothpick Tortoise
          Toucan Triceratops Tritium Trousers Trumpet Tuba Tugboat Turnip Turtle Tuxedo
          Tyrannosaurus Ukulele Umbrella Unicorn Unicycle Universe Uranium Urchin
          Utahraptor Vampire Velociraptor Vindaloo Volcano Vulcan Vulcanodon Vulture
          Waffle Walrus Warthog Waterfowl Watermelon Weasel Whatchamacallit Whodunit
          Wiggles Wildebeest Wingnut Wizard Wombat Wookie Worm Wormhole Wrigglesworth
          Xylophone Yak Yodeler Yogurt Yoyo Ytterbium Yurt Zamboni Zebra Zephyr Zeppelin
          Zither Zombie Zucchini
        </Markov>
      </Join>
    </Join>
    <Option id="suffix" probability="0.3">
      <Switch>
        <Switch>
          <Join>
            <Literal text=", " />
            <Words id="postnominal">
              CA DDS DVM Esq. Jr. MD MP OBE PhD Sr. VC
            </Words>
          </Join>
          <Join>
            <Literal text=" " />
            <Number id="ordinal" min="1" max="29" style="RomanUpper" />
          </Join>
        </Switch>
        <Join>
          <Literal text=" the " />
          <Words id="epithet">
            Adorable Amazing Amusing Angry Anxious Apprehensive Arrogant Awesome Awkward Bad
            Barbarian Beautiful Bewildered Bizarre Blithering Boastful Brash Brave
            Cantankerous Cheeky Chilly Chubby Chubby Chummy Chunky Churlish Clever Clueless
            Clumsy Clumsy Colossal Comical Confused Cool Cranky Crazy Cryptic Curmudgeonly
            Dapper Devious Diligent Discombocbulated Disgruntled Dreadful Drunken Eccentric
            Elegant Elusive Embarrassed Enigmatic Eternal Evil Exasperated Excellent
            Exceptional Excited Extraordinary Fabulous Fantastic Fierce Flabbergasted
            Flammable Fluffy Foolish Fragrant Frightened Funky Funny Furious Fuzzy Glorious
            Good Great Grim Grizzled Groovy Grouchy Grumpy Handsome Hangry Happy Heavy
            Helpless Hideous Hilarious Holy Huggable Humble Humorous Hyperbolic Iconic
            Imaginative Impish Important Impossible Impressive Improbable Incomprehensible
            Inconceivable Incredible Incredulous Indignant Ingenious Inquisitive Inscrutable
            Intrepid Ironic Irrational Irrelevant Irreverent Irritable Jealous Jolly Jovial
            Joyous Jubilant Judicious Jumpy Kooky Lanky Lazy Legendary Lethargic Loopy
            Loquacious Loud Lovely Ludicrous Lyrical Mad Magical Magnificent Maladroit
            Malodorous Maniac Marvelous Mischievous Miserable Mistaken Modest Monstrous
            Monumental Morbid Mysterious Nasty Naughty Nefarious Noble Noisy Nonchalant
            Nonplussed Nonsensical Normal Nosy Noxious Nutty Obese Obnoxious Occupied
            Octagonal Odd Offensive Ogre Old Ominous Oneiric Optimistic Ordinary Original
            Ornery Outrageous Outstanding Panicky Paranoid Pathetic Peculiar Perfect Perky
            Perplexed Petty Phantasmagorical Philosophical Pompous Preposterous Proud
            Psychotic Putrid Puzzling Quaint Qualified Quintessential Quixotic Quizzical
            Rambunctious Rascally Reclusive Regal Relevant Reluctant Remarkable Repulsive
            Resilient Respectable Restless Robust Rude Ruthless Sad Sarcastic Sassy
            Secretive Serious Shady Shameless Shifty Shy Silly Sleepy Slippery Slothful
            Smelly Smug Snarky Soggy Spiffy Spunky Stately Stubborn Sublime Superfluous
            Suspicious Swaggering Swanky Swift Tactful Talented Tenacious Terrible Thankful
            Theological Thoughtful Thoughtless Thundering Timid Trickster Troubling
            Ubiquitous Ugly Unacceptable Unbelievable Uncanny Undead Unflappable
            Unforgettable Unimpressive Unpronounceable Unruly Unscrupulous Unstoppable
            Upbeat Upset Upstanding Urgent Useful Vagrant Valiant Valid Valorous Vapid
            Vegetarian Vehement Versatile Vexing Vibrant Vicious Victorious Vigilant
            Vindictive Vivacious Vulgar Wacky Wandering Wanted Weird Wise Wistful Wizard
            Wonderful Wretched Yawning Yummy Zany Zealous Zesty
          </Words>
        </Join>
      </Switch>
    </Option>
  </Join>
</NameGen>
